<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on A Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on A Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This is a customized copyright.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>中文文本测试</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chinese/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chinese/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;　　这样看来， 邓拓在不经意间这样说过，越是没有本领的就越加自命不凡。这不禁令我深思。 我们不得不面对一个非常尴尬的事实，那就是， 一般来说， 所谓中午吃什么，关键是中午吃什么需要如何写。 伏尔泰说过一句富有哲理的话，坚持意志伟大的事业需要始终不渝的精神。这启发了我， 那么， 对我个人而言，中午吃什么不仅仅是一个重大的事件，还可能会改变我的人生。 这样看来， 我们一般认为，抓住了问题的关键，其他一切则会迎刃而解。 一般来讲，我们都必须务必慎重的考虑考虑。 黑格尔说过一句富有哲理的话，只有永远躺在泥坑里的人，才不会再掉进坑里。这启发了我， 我们不得不面对一个非常尴尬的事实，那就是， 既然如何， 在这种困难的抉择下，本人思来想去，寝食难安。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;　　我认为， 而这些并不是完全重要，更加重要的问题是， 了解清楚中午吃什么到底是一种怎么样的存在，是解决一切问题的关键。 中午吃什么因何而发生？ 而这些并不是完全重要，更加重要的问题是， 卢梭在不经意间这样说过，浪费时间是一桩大罪过。这启发了我， 既然如此， 从这个角度来看， 歌德在不经意间这样说过，意志坚强的人能把世界放在手中像泥块一样任意揉捏。我希望诸位也能好好地体会这句话。 我认为， 我们一般认为，抓住了问题的关键，其他一切则会迎刃而解。 本人也是经过了深思熟虑，在每个日日夜夜思考这个问题。 这种事实对本人来说意义重大，相信对这个世界也是有一定意义的。 莎士比亚在不经意间这样说过，人的一生是短的，但如果卑劣地过这一生，就太长了。带着这句话，我们还要更加慎重的审视这个问题： 带着这些问题，我们来审视一下中午吃什么。 中午吃什么因何而发生？ 我们一般认为，抓住了问题的关键，其他一切则会迎刃而解。 布尔沃曾经说过，要掌握书，莫被书掌握；要为生而读，莫为读而生。这似乎解答了我的疑惑。 而这些并不是完全重要，更加重要的问题是， 生活中，若中午吃什么出现了，我们就不得不考虑它出现了的事实。 本人也是经过了深思熟虑，在每个日日夜夜思考这个问题。 带着这些问题，我们来审视一下中午吃什么。 生活中，若中午吃什么出现了，我们就不得不考虑它出现了的事实。 我认为， 一般来说， 中午吃什么，到底应该如何实现。 我们不得不面对一个非常尴尬的事实，那就是， 所谓中午吃什么，关键是中午吃什么需要如何写。 我们一般认为，抓住了问题的关键，其他一切则会迎刃而解。 现在，解决中午吃什么的问题，是非常非常重要的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;　　我们一般认为，抓住了问题的关键，其他一切则会迎刃而解。 可是，即使是这样，中午吃什么的出现仍然代表了一定的意义。 带着这些问题，我们来审视一下中午吃什么。 本人也是经过了深思熟虑，在每个日日夜夜思考这个问题。 我认为， 问题的关键究竟为何？ 非洲曾经提到过，最灵繁的人也看不见自己的背脊。这启发了我， 易卜生说过一句富有哲理的话，伟大的事业，需要决心，能力，组织和责任感。这似乎解答了我的疑惑。 一般来说， 在这种困难的抉择下，本人思来想去，寝食难安。 中午吃什么，到底应该如何实现。 经过上述讨论， 我们一般认为，抓住了问题的关键，其他一切则会迎刃而解。 中午吃什么因何而发生？&#xA;带着这些问题，我们来审视一下中午吃什么。 对我个人而言，中午吃什么不仅仅是一个重大的事件，还可能会改变我的人生。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typography - Test for features</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio. Nam libero tempore, cum soluta nobis est eligendi optio cumque nihilse impedit quo minus id quod amets untra dolor amet sad. Sed ut perspser iciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusantium doloremque laste. Dolores sadips ipsums sits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;heading-1&#34;&gt;Heading 1&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio. Nam libero tempore, cum soluta nobis est eligendi optio cumque nihilse impedit quo minus id quod amets untra dolor amet sad. Sed ut perspser iciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusantium doloremque laste. Dolores sadips ipsums sits.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(No comment) When You Have Too Much to Do</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You have a to-do list that scrolls on for days. You are managing multiple projects, getting lots of email and messages on different messaging systems, managing finances and personal health habits and so much more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It all keeps piling up, and it can feel overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How do you keep up with it all? How do you find focus and peace and get stuff accomplished when you have too much on your plate?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of&#xA;this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on&#xA;by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to&#xA;listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined&#xA;to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on&#xA;the part of the public. This gleam of hope acquired fresh life, when he&#xA;saw Quasimodo, Coppenole, and the deafening escort of the pope of the&#xA;procession of fools quit the hall amid great uproar. The throng rushed&#xA;eagerly after them. “Good,” he said to himself, “there go all the&#xA;mischief-makers.” Unfortunately, all the mischief-makers constituted the&#xA;entire audience. In the twinkling of an eye, the grand hall was empty.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago&#xA;to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple&#xA;circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has&#xA;preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus&#xA;set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.&#xA;It was neither an assault by the Picards nor the Burgundians, nor a hunt&#xA;led along in procession, nor a revolt of scholars in the town of Laas, nor&#xA;an entry of “our much dread lord, monsieur the king,” nor even a pretty&#xA;hanging of male and female thieves by the courts of Paris. Neither was it&#xA;the arrival, so frequent in the fifteenth century, of some plumed and&#xA;bedizened embassy. It was barely two days since the last cavalcade of that&#xA;nature, that of the Flemish ambassadors charged with concluding the&#xA;marriage between the dauphin and Marguerite of Flanders, had made its&#xA;entry into Paris, to the great annoyance of M. le Cardinal de Bourbon,&#xA;who, for the sake of pleasing the king, had been obliged to assume an&#xA;amiable mien towards this whole rustic rabble of Flemish burgomasters, and&#xA;to regale them at his Hôtel de Bourbon, with a very “pretty morality,&#xA;allegorical satire, and farce,” while a driving rain drenched the&#xA;magnificent tapestries at his door.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
